xhamsterpremium.com 2019-12-13

# Privacy policy

_Effective Date: May 26, 2017  
Last Modified: May 26, 2017  
Website(s) covered: xhamsterpremium.com_

### General

The operative parties referred to in this policy are Company and You, the User of this site.

ТЕСOМ LТD a limited liability company registered in the Republic of Cyprus with registration number: ΗΕ 365144 and registered address located at: 132 Arch. Makariou III, Sagro Building, 3021 Limassol, CYPRUS is the publisher and operator of the Website(s) listed at the beginning of this Policy. Hereinafter, ТЕСOМ LТD shall be referred to as “Company”. When first-person pronouns are used in this Policy, (Us, We, Our, Ours, etc.) these provisions are referring to Company. Additionally, when the terms “the Site” or “Site” are used, these terms refer to the website(s) listed at the beginning of this Policy. You, the User – As the User of this Site, this Policy will refer to the User as “You” or through any applicable second-person pronouns, such as “Yours,” etc. Hereinafter, the User of the Site shall be referred to in applicable second-person pronouns.

This Privacy Policy describes how we use information received about You when You visit Our Site, or otherwise use Our online services. This Policy does not cover any information that We may receive from or about You through channels other than through the use of the Site.

Pursuant to our Terms of Use, this document describes how we treat personal information related to your use of this website and the services offered on and through it (the “Service”), including information you provide when using it.

We expressly and strictly limit use of the Service to adults over 18 years of age or the age of majority in the individual’s jurisdiction, whichever is greater. Anyone under this age is strictly forbidden from using the Service. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons who have not attained this age.

### Data Collected

_Browsing the Website._ You can use the search function, view articles, videos and pictures, and access other parts of the Service without having an account, in which case only your IP address, country of origin and other information about your computer or device (such as web requests, device type, browser type, browser language, referring URL, operating system and date and time of requests) will be recorded for log file information, aggregated traffic information and in the event that there is any misappropriation of information and/or content. If you have an account on the website and are logged in, the information may be associated with your account.

_Registering on the Website._ Registration of an account is required for using many parts of the Service, including purchasing access to certain content and using many other features. We request additional information at the time of your registration, including, without limitation, your name, email address and a password. Your IP address is recorded automatically. We may ask for further information to fill out your profile details. Some of this information may be used to provide you the Service and may become publicly available through your profile or through other use of the Service. If you intend to make your content available on the Service, we will collect additional information necessary to confirm your authority, confirm your compliance with law and to make available where necessary on the Service for others.

_Usage Information._ We may record information about your usage of the Service such as pageviews, clicks, mousemoves, duration of video views, portions of videos viewed, search phrases, referrers and other various statistics. If you have registered and are logged in, we may associate that information with your account.

_Uploaded Content._ Any personal information or content you voluntarily publicly disclose online, including animations, pictures, videos, comments and your profile page or any other User Submissions, becomes publicly available and may be collected and used by others.

_Other Information._ You may have the ability to make comments on content and engage in other social activities. Any such activities may be visible to the public.

_Correspondences._ We may keep a record of any correspondence between you and us.

_Cookies._ When you use the Service, we may send cookies to your computer to uniquely identify your browser session. We may use both session cookies and permanent cookies. For more information please refer to our Cookies policy.

_Payment Information_. We do not keep in our system any of your payment information such as credit cards, debit cards or bank account information. This information is only provided to our third party payment processors and affiliates in order to assist with the taking or making of payments. 

### Data Usage

We may use your information to provide you with certain features and to create a personalized experience on the Service. We may also use that information to operate, maintain and improve features and functionality of the Service, including building a recommendation system for the Service.

We may use your e-mail address or other personal information to send commercial or marketing messages. We may use your e-mail for non-marketing or administrative purposes.

We use cookies, web beacons and other information to store information so that you will not have to re-enter it on future visits, provide personalized content and information, monitor the effectiveness of the Service and monitor aggregate metrics such as the number of visitors and page views (including for use in monitoring visitors from affiliates). They may also be used to provide targeted advertising based on your country of origin and other personal information.

We may aggregate your personal information with personal information of other members and users, and disclose such information to advertisers and other third-parties for marketing and promotional purposes.

Your username may be displayed to other visitors of the Service alongside content on the Service in relation to your uploaded content and other similar features.

We may use your information to run promotions, contests, surveys and other features and events.

### Disclosures of Information

We may be required to release certain data to comply with legal obligations or in order to enforce our Terms of Use and other agreements. We may also release certain data to protect the rights, property or safety of us, our users and others. This includes providing information to other companies or organizations like the police or governmental authorities for the purposes of protection against or prosecution of any illegal activity, whether or not it is identified in the Terms of Use.

If you upload any illegal or unauthorized material to the Service, or you are suspected of doing such, we may forward all available information to relevant authorities, including respective copyright owners, without any notice to you.

We may also share your information with third parties for the purposes of payment processing and any such information will also be subject to their privacy policies.

### Miscellaneous

If you have an account on the Service and have a password giving you access to certain parts of the Service, you are responsible for keeping the password confidential. Anyone else with your password may access your account and other personal information.

While we use commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to secure your information, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information or content you transmit to us. Any information or content you transmit to us is done at your own risk.
